

Mugia Miftahul Choir

Address: Cicadas, Sagalaherang, Subang, Jawa Barat, Indonesia, 41282, Subang, Indonesia

Email address: mugia.miftahul@gmail.com

Phone number: (+62) 83816355113 **Website:** https://mugia.herokuapp.com/

Whatsapp Messenger: +62 83816355113

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/mugia-choir-3b593a1b4/

O Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/mugiadesign/

Date of birth: 18/06/2001 Nationality: Indonesian

ABOUT ME

I'm a university student at Universitas Komputer Indonesia majoring in information systems. I have an interest in Web Development and 3D design. I've gained experience working on a different scale of projects, from individual projects to corporate class projects. Yet I still have great determination in learning new stuff. I also have experience of working with people from different countries and cultures such as British, so I can communicate well with others and am capable of working alone or inside a team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

[06/2020 - 02/2021] **Web developer**

MTs Al-Hidayah Sagalaherang

City: Subang

Country: Indonesia

Main activities and responsibilities:

I held all of the jobs in the web development process by myself, including: doing a brief with the client, sketching, wireframing, prototyping, creating high fidelity UI design, designing and implementing a database, front-end, and back-end job

[04/2020 - 06/2021] **Web developer**

SMAN 1 Jalancagak Scout Organization

City: Subang

Country: Indonesia

Main activities and responsibilities:

My responsibilities were designing the UI of the website, developing the website according to the design, designing and implementing a database, giving the required training for the users, and maintaining the website after it was online

[03/09/2021 - 10/02/2022] **3D artist**

RFIDiom Ltd

City: Liverpool

Country: United Kingdom

Main activities and responsibilities:

I was a part of the Marketing Team at RFIDiom Ltd; my main activities were creating graphics content for social media, or blog. But I also contributed to Branding a few of the company's products. And designing UI/UX of a product website.

My special responsibilities were to create 3D assets and create 3D animations; usually, they were used to demo or advertise products.

On occasions I was also responsible for quality assurance on some websites, looking for errors, bugs, etc.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

[30/06/2021 - 03/07/2021] Digital Marketing and Graphic Design Training

PT Inovasi Telematika Nusantara VirtualTraining.id

[30/12/2020 - 15/02/2021] **Web & Mobille Design Training**

Zero to Mastery zerotomastery.io

[03/11/2020 - 27/12/2020] **React.js Training**

Zero to Mastery zerotomastery.io

[04/03/2021 - 04/04/2021] **React Native Training**

Zero to Mastery zerotomastery.io

 $\hbox{\tt [10/06/2020-29/06/2020]} \ \textbf{Fundamental Front-End Web Development Training}$

Dicoding dicoding.com

[17/06/2021 - 08/09/2021] **3D Modeling Training**

GameDev.tv gamedev.tv

[14/09/2021 - 27/09/2021] 3D Character Creator for Video Games Training

GameDev.tv gamedev.tv

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Indonesian

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING C1 READING B2 WRITING B2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2

My Digital Skills

Design

Adobe Photoshop | Corel Draw | Adobe Illustrator | Figma

Programming

React ecosystem: ReactJS, React Router, Redux, Typescript | HTML5/CSS3, SASS, JavaScript (including recent versions) | PHP Laravel | Javascript ECMA6

3D

Blender, 3D modeling | 3D animation